重庆市二零二零年初中学业水平暨高中招生考试英语听力测试部分。第一。节听一遍。根据你所听到的句子，从三个选项中选出最恰当的答语。每小题你将有七秒钟的时间读题和答题
重庆第二节，听一遍。根据你所听到的对话。和问题，从
,B,B Hello mom, this is Jack.
三个选项中选出正确答案。每小题你将有八秒钟的时间读题和答题。
第三节。听两遍。根据你所听到的长对话，从三个选项中选出正确答案。听长对话前，你将有十秒钟的时间阅读各个小题。听完后，你将有十秒钟的时间。先答题。听第一段材料，回答第十三和十四小题。
How is everything at home?
Good. What about you?
Not bad. What's the weather like in Beijing today?
It's very cold.
That's terrible. Put on more clothes and take care.
I will. When are you coming back?
Next Tuesday. Sorry mom, have to go now.
Bye. Hello mom, this is Jack.
How is everything at home?
Good. What about you?
Not bad. What's the weather like in Beijing today?
It's very cold.
That's terrible. Put on more clothes and take care.
I will. When are you coming back?
Next Tuesday. Sorry mom, have to go now.
Bye. Dad, what are you doing?
听第二段材料，回答第十五和十六小题。
I'm watching a volleyball match.
Oh, the Chinese women's volleyball team.
Yeah, they are so great.
Do you know a new movie about them is coming out?
Yes, I do.
I'm looking forward to it.
So am I.
Let's go and watch it when it comes out.
Okay. Their spirit of never giving up encourages all Chinese.
That's right. We should learn from them.
Dad, what are you doing?
I'm watching a volleyball match.
Oh, the Chinese women's volleyball team.
Yeah, they are so great.
Do you know a new movie about them is coming out?
Yes, I do.
I'm looking forward to it.
So am I.
Let's go and watch it when it comes out.
Okay. Their spirit of never giving up encourages all Chinese.
That's right.,B Hello, everyone.
我们应从他们第四节听两遍。根据你所听到的短文内容，从一三个选项中选出正确答案。听短文前，你将有二十秒钟的时间阅读各个小题；听完后，你将有二十秒钟的时间答题。
I'm your guide today.
My name is Sandy.
are setting off to the King Palace.
Before leaving, I'd like to tell you a few things.
Please pay attention.
We have three groups on this trip, and there are three tourist buses for us.
We are on bus number two.
The palace is probably very busy.
If you get lost, go towards the gate, and you will find me at the ticket office.
Now, the palace is a
But you will be surprised to find that people still live there.
Are they kings?
Of course not.
They are local people who work at the palace.
Many of them wear traditional clothes, so it will be great to take photos with them.
But please ask them if it's okay before doing this.
That's all. Have a good time.
Hello, everyone. I'm your guide today.
My name is Sandy.
are setting off to the King Palace.
Before leaving, I'd like to tell you a few things.
Please pay attention.
We have three groups on this trip, and there are three tourist buses for us.
We are on bus number two.
The palace is probably very busy.
If you get lost, go towards the gate, and you will find me at the ticket office.
Now, the palace is a
But you will be surprised to find that people still live there.
Are they kings?
Of course not.
They are local people who work at the palace.
Many of them wear traditional clothes, so it will be great to take photos with them.
But please ask them if it's okay before doing this.
That's all. Have a good time.
you
听力测试完毕。